export default [
  {
    id: 1,
    question:
      "Thailand .......... by some of the worst flooding in decades late last year.",
    options: ["was hit", "was hitting", "was being hit", "hit"],
    // answer: "was hit"
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      '"In January 2012 Yahoo ........ Scott Thompson, the president of online payments firm Paypal, as its new head."',
    options: ["was naming", "named", "name", "has named"],
    // "answer": "named"
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "Before ....... Yahoo Mr. Thompson served as president of online payments firm PayPal from 2008.",
    options: ["joined", "being joined", "joining", "was joined"],
    // "answer": "joined"
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      '"Yahoo\'s stock ........ since it passed up a $44bn takeover bid from Microsoft in 2008."',
    options: [
      "was languished",
      '"have languished"',
      "languished",
      '"has languished"',
    ],
    // "answer": "languished"
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      "Last year, the Chinese government stopped ........ nationwide home price statistics, and now only reports data on specific cities.",
    options: ["providing", "to provide", "provide", "provides"],
    // "answer": "providing"
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "At the same time, the recent drop in oil prices ......... to keep consumer price growth in check.",
    options: ["has also helped", "have also helped", "also helps", "also help"],
    // "answer": "has also helped"
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "During the first quarter of 2012 the Chinese economy ....... at a pace of 8.1%.",
    options: ["grown", "grew", "grows", "has grown"],
    // "answer": "grew"
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      '"For its part, the EU welcomed the G8 communiqué with its dual emphasis on ....... growth and jobs."',
    options: ["to boost", "boosting", "boost", "boosts"],
    // "answer": "to boost"
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "The worry is that if property prices ......... further then it will hurt growth in the world's second-largest economy.",
    options: ["falls", "fell", "fall", '"have fallen"'],
    // "answer": "fall"
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "It has been noticeable that since last Wednesday, Number 10 .......... towards more evidence-based policy.",
    options: ["have been moving", "have moved", "has been moving", "moved"],
    // "answer": "have moved"
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question:
      "Yahoo ........ that Mr. Thompson, who took up his post in January, does not have a computer science degree.",
    options: [
      "already acknowledging",
      "already acknowledged",
      "have already acknowledged",
      '"has already acknowledged"',
    ],
    // "answer": "already acknowledged"
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question:
      '"Investment firm Third Point discovered that Mr. Thompson did not hold a degree in computer science as ........."',
    options: [
      "had been claimed",
      "has been claimed",
      "been claimed",
      "being claimed",
    ],
    // "answer": "had been claimed"
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question:
      "On Monday the Wall Street Journal reported that Mr. Thompson, 54, told Yahoo's board late last week he ........... with thyroid cancer.",
    options: [
      "had been diagnosed",
      "has been diagnosed",
      "was diagnosed",
      "is diagnosed",
    ],
    // "answer": "had been diagnosed"
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question:
      '"President Obama said leaders ......... good progress on a range of issues."',
    options: ["having made", "had made", "have made", "was made"],
    // "answer": "having made"
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question:
      '"Leaders ........ the summit addressed a number of issues, including energy security, climate change and the situation in Iran, Afghanistan and North Korea."',
    options: ["attended", "attending", "attend", "attends"],
    // "answer": "attended"
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question:
      '"He will also be able .......... two other new directors, while Yahoo has named Fred Amoroso as the new chairman of its board."',
    options: ["appoint", "to appoint", "appointing", "appoints"],
    // "answer": "to appoint"
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question:
      '"Third Point believes that Yahoo shareholders and employees will be best served if the board .......... responsibility quickly for this latest debacle."',
    options: ["accepting", "accepts", "accepted", "is accepting"],
    // "answer": "accepted"
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question:
      '"In an earlier communiqué, G8 leaders committed themselves to promoting growth alongside fiscal responsibility and affirmed that they wanted Greece ........... in the eurozone."',
    options: ["stayed", "to stay", "stay", "staying"],
    // "answer": "to stay"
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question:
      "If it falls below that figure, they argue, the country may find it more difficult ........ domestic demand, boost infrastructure investment and accelerate job creation.",
    options: ["maintain", "maintaining", "to maintaining", "to maintain"],
    // "answer": "to maintain"
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question:
      "China has been trying to boost domestic demand in an attempt ......... the fall in global demand for its exports.",
    options: ["to offset", "to offset", "offset", "offsetting", "offsets"],
    // "answer": "to offset"
  },
];

export const answers = [
  0, 1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 1, 2, 3, 3, 0, 1, 3, 2, 1, 3, 0,
];
